

Luca Vigotti

Front-End Developer

PROFILE

Multilingual professional from Italy with a passion for Front End Development.

I discovered this passion when I worked as an IT Recruitment Consultant. When I started researching the industry I tried coding to better understand the roles I was recruiting for. Doing this I realized coding is what I want to do. I have lived on every continent but Antarctica and I have worked with people from all over the world. Now my journey has me as a developer in Japan.

EDUCATION

Web Development Bootcamp

LeWagon Tokyo

01/2023 - 03/2023 Tokyo, Japan

BA in Psychology

Vancouver Island University

09/2015 - 06/2019 Nanaimo, BC, Canada

Japanese Language Student

Yoshida Institute of Japanese Language

10/2019 - 09/2020 Tokyo, Japan

PROJECTS

Portfolio &

Personal portfolio used to show my skills and projects

Kotoback &

- Users can upload epub ebooks which are automatically translated and turned into flashcards. I primarily worked on the Front End. I was in charge of all the UI and UX aspects of the app.
- HTML5, CSS, Javascript, Ruby on Rails

Haunted Tours 🔗

- Spooky tour ideas based on the Airbnb model which allows you to host and/or book a tour.
- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails

Hidden Nerima 🔗

• This project comes from the idea to showing people the hidden gems that can be found in the Nerima Ward. Users can discover new locations and add their own. A chat system is coming soon.

SKILLS

HTML5 | CSS | SCSS | JavaScript | Stimulus.js | React | Ruby | Ruby on Rails | Figma

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

English Teacher

05/2020 - 12/2022

Saiei Internation, Progress English Camp Tokyo, Japan

• Over 80% of the students was able to pass the TOEIC/EIKEN test.

06/2021 - 02/2022 Tokyo, Japan

Recruitment Consultant

KLAR K.K

- Searched for the best talents in IT and Digital Marketing.
- Assisted candidates and clients finding the best match for them.

LANGUAGES

Italian: Native | English: Native level | Japanese: Limited working proficiency